# Steven Jackson

Software Engineer

Jalan Mendeka, Labuan F. T., Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 87000 | +6087427744

steven.jackson.1989@tutamail.com



A Software Engineer with 10+ years of experience specializing in project management, cloud technology, application development, and Python. A strong history of executing complex projects to design, test, and deliver innovative software solutions to enterprise clients.

## **Professional Experience**

## **Wednesday Solutions**

July 2018 - February 2024

#### **Software Engineer**

- Developed and implemented new AI game "Chinese Checkers" using programming languages such as Java, Python, Reinfocement Learning, and C++
- Developed applications and microservices of multi-threaded, high-load (from 2K requests/sec), designing such services, making architectural decisions.
- Designed and optimized databases to improve data storage of offline Android Dictionary efficiency and retrieval speed

## **Webby Group**

August 2010 - June 2018

#### **Full Stack Developer**

- Designed and developed user-friendly interfaces for multiple web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Vue.js.
- Utilized various programming languages such as Python, Ruby, Laravel, Perl and Java to build scalable backend systems for handling large volumes of data
- Support the development of several mobile applications and games in iOS and Android environments
- Manage a team of five developers to design 12 web applications to process, analyze, and render data, including the development of new features to improve data visualization

### **Education**

#### Computer System Security in Information Technology & Business Technology

April 2006 - May 2010

University Kuala Lumpur, 1016, Jalan Sultan Ismail, 50250 Kuala Lumpur

## **Key Skills**

1C programming, Docker, Django Framework, Golang, 1C-Bitrix, Integral, Vue, REST API, Node.js, ClickHouse, amoCRM, Unity, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Java/Spring, PHP/CI/Laravel, Linux/Android, MySQL/PostgreSQL/MongoDB/SQLite, Python/PyTorch, MFC/Qt, AutoCAD/Solidworks, ASM/C/C++/C#/VBA/Rust, Perl, Vue.js